[{"answer": "You'll get in when I get my rent", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Sure. You're good for it every time this happens", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What if I do it moderate? I could hold back on certain moves. There's always ways to fak", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "One more", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Don't you wanna get even? I whipped your butt", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Shit. When", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You can't talk here", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Doctor says I can't wrestle no more", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't know. I don't know what to do. If I can't wrestle..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "We don't really get along too good", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " She don't need me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Man, I worked up a pretty good thirst in there. What say we grab a beer", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "One beer! We gotta r", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Who cares? Fuckin' Def Lep", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Fine. Then I'm dancing for you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " I totally didn't realize the time", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I should get home", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You'd hop on my foot and wrap your arms around my leg. I'd have to walk you the whole way through like that", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Do what", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What if we'd met someplace else", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "But what if we did", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We didn't", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "We didn't", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "But what if we did", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What if we did", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "We didn't", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "We didn't", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "We didn't", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You're a customer. You're just a fucking customer. That's it. Okay? Got it", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You didn't fuck up. You are a fuc", "docId": "Wrestler_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Just please shut the fuck up. Because I can't even stand the sound of your voice. ", "qsentId": 34}]